Siva Charan

Business Developer

Good Knowledge in Premium cars and Automatic Transmission vehicles.

Ability to work without any supervision

Good organizational skills and General Knowledge

Team building and targeting

Private Properties dealing in and out of city with big shots up-to 500 Acres.

Business Development Manager with 6+ years of hands-on experience in business development, key accounts management, and strategic relationship development. Proven history of driving significant revenue growth and profitability within highly competitive markets.

Employment History

Associate Director & Script Coordination at Mythri Movie Makers, Hyderabad

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

Working as Direction Department and Script Coordination "Mythri Movie Makers" into 2 Projects. TFI Hyderabad.

Admin & Sales Product Manager at Vibrrant Ventures, Hyderabad

APRIL 2019 - JULY 2021

Worked in Vibrrant Ventures as Admin and Product Sales and Team Leader in Indo Qatar Projects pvt ltd.

Business Process Analyst at HSBC Falken, Hyderabad

FEBRUARY 2018 - MARCH 2019

Worked in HSBC Falken as Business Process Outsource for 1 year, Hyderabad

Visual Effects Compositor at RamaNaidu Studios, Hyderabad

JANUARY 2017 - AUGUST 2018

Worked as Visual Effects Compositor for 15 months in Prime Focus Lab, RamaNaidu Studios, Hyderabad.

Marketing Executive at V4i Security Systems & Home Automation

OCTOBER 2016 - DECEMBER 2017

Worked as Marketing Executive in V4i security systems and Home Automation for 8months, Hyderabad.

Details

Hyderabad, India +91 8106266264.

sivacharan.dharanikota@gmail.com

Skills

Ability to Work in a Team

Fast Learner

Ability to Multitask

Microsoft Office

Communication Skills

Business Development

Computer skills:

Multimedia & Visual Effects

Relationship Management

Sales experience and strategy

Education

10th board exam at Teja High School, Sriharikota

2023

82.1

Intermediate at Nalanda junior oollege, Hyderabad

2005

67.3

B.com(computers) at Dr. B.R. Ambedkar Open University, Hyderabad

2009

70.5